this is the time known as the great pirate era a countless array of pirates go to battle across
the seas in search of the one piece the legendary treasure left behind by gold watcher king of the
pirates monkey and luffy a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit set sail
to become the next king of the pirates as luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles they
capture the unwanted attention of the world government which will use any means necessary
to stop them this site can't wait to see what kind of adventures up next with a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue the crew will cut a path across the grand line to the new world
after being separated from his crew luffy set out to rescue his brother ace from the navy
to do so he snuck into impelled down the greatest prison in the world with the assistance of
yvonne cough the queen of newcomer land luffy made it all the way to level six where ace was being
detained impelled down hereby transfers custody of the criminal pork sd ace to the navy forces present
today but luffy was too late ace was already on a ship headed toward navy headquarters
i'm going to marine ford after releasing jean bay and luffy's former enemy crocodile from their cells
luffy's mob prepares to storm level four even more chaos blackbeard teach invades
come on hurry up there's a lot of commotion out there
all prison staff head to level four now repeat all prison staff to level four
they just made an announcement but i couldn't hear it
perhaps something big is happening downstairs hey take a look bucky all the jailers in the blue
corner you're making a retreat all prison staff head down to level four now it looks like they're
clearing out all the beasts get the hell out of here you filthy monsters yeah don't ever come back
something big must be happening on one of the other levels now's our chance to make a break ford
partner it's like a dream come true
we've been through so much haunted by the army wolves in level five
and then we were sicked by the lingering noxious clouds of a challenge poison on level four
this this must be magellan's work
and don't forget about level three having to face off against the sphinx again
and the latest indignity pretending to be part of the floor to escape the wild beasts
we've been stuck in some cruel cosmic joke is nothing but comic relief
but we made it all the way to level two
just a little bit further now and we'll be out of this hellhole
well boys ready to break out ready as ever
my compliments to mr. three on these wax keys
some fine craftsmanship right here
all guards report to level four
get me team in here
what the hell's taking so long
we've lost touch with c team
we need backup
come in vice warden
this is the monitoring room please come in
what's wrong
this looks strange
what
no no it's not as weird as it looks i'll explain
you see i secretly ordered this fancy headdress to more clearly assert my authority when i became warden
that's all
i'm not talking about your weird headdress
we've got a visual feed on someone sneaking around on level two
and they look like prisoners
what did you say
thanks buddy
don't thank me
thank captain buggy
round up the guards left on two
get their butts over there now
yes sir
any guards left on two
anyone
answer me if you're still there
yes sir
are you doing anything crucial at the moment
um we were just heading down to level four as ordered
make a full inspection of level two instead
this floor
now's our chance partner
you ready
once the guards are distracted by the riot
we'll sneak out of here and stow away on a navy ship
we're so close and we'll go down in history for breaking out of this nightmare prison
i'd wait a straw hat and mr. two are already dead by now
either that or they'll spend the rest of their miserable lives in this hell
well that sure is a sad thought right there
but at least we saved our own asses
oh
i've got eyes on buggy the clown
and look
he's got mr. three with him
level two
look up
all right you guys if you want your freedom back this is your chance
now let's tear this place apart fight like you got nothing left to lose
let's kick it all
give it up for our savior
yeah captain buggy
come in
level two here
i don't know how but the fishers are out of their cells and writing again
they're out of control
we need the bugody back
send backup
come in level four here
oh what is it now
we found ivanka and inazuma
not only that but they've got the guy who tricked you with them mr. two
hee-haw
can't break me i break it out
they're storming level four with an entire mob
what a mob
all staff get down to level four immediately
every available guard
you're not going to believe this
but the mob they've got with them
they're all of the missing prisoners
the inmates who've disappeared over the years by demoning the world
trying checking again
that can't be right
i know what i'm looking at
okay i need to know
can i still be the warden
yee-haw i finally caught up with you
hey straw boy
clay looks like you got your juices flowing again
yeah i'm better than ever now
hang on why are you here mr. one
you hear me
huh you know that guy
yeah and so do you
your swordsman buddy defeated him back in alabaster
oh sorry not ringing any bells for me
vice warden
we need more backup on level four
we also need more guys on level two
this isn't there
we need backup now
vice warden give us an order
send the guards to level four
no send us to level two
yes warden we need your orders
imperio face growth synthesis
ah
yee-haw
hurry it's running here
hell
whee
that's too many we can't stop them
they're already vicious enough when we lock them away
ah
but now they're vicious and super weird
fish man karate
or a best
brick fist
whence
Joe
there's no tiny
fall
this day
can we hype the
Brusca
you乐
win
ri
no
turn to Smith
at the game
we can't stop them
let's go straight to navy head quarter
yeah
we've received word from impel down
We've received word from Impel Down. An unprecedented riot has broken out and shut down the entire prison.
The ringleader of this revolt is none other than Monkey D. Luffy.
Enjoy the view while you still can.
Once you've been shackled onto the scaffold, I can promise you this.
You'll never see the sky again.
This is Onigumo. We're now approaching. Prepare to open the gate of Marine Ford.
Fleet Admiral Sengoku!
How did it go?
We still haven't found him yet.
Ace's execution is five hours from now, so we don't exactly have time in our favor.
Whitebeard could launch an attack any moment now.
We need a warlord on our side! We've searched the whole island!
We can't find Blackbeard! He's gone missing!
And this could be unrelated, but we just received word of a Navy ship.
Arriving at Impel Down without any clearance.
What?
I know, sir, but what are the chances it's him?
What? Why would he come here?
I want you to conduct a thorough search of the ship they arrived on.
Sir!
Please, wait a sec. We didn't request any reinforcements.
And we're in the midst of a state of emergency, so we can't assure your safety.
We're waiting to hear back from headquarters at the moment.
Don't go pissing your britches. We're all on the same side.
That's not the issue!
No pirate is allowed to step foot inside the prison, even if you're on...
Don't bother holding back with these guys.
After all, we're the highest-ranking officials here!
Captain, there's not a single crew member left alive on the ship Blackbeard came in on!
They're dead?
Hey, sir!
Don't take another step!
We have an intruder!
The Warlord of the Sea, Marshal D. Teach!
Hey, are you all right? Blackbeard sucked them all up and spit them back out!
The darkness...
Blackbeard and his crew are breaking into the prison, and I don't think we can stop them!
The darkness! It swallowed me up all!
His motive is unknown!
We need your order, sir! Please hurry!
It's over! My entire life is over!
No! I wish it was over! This is just the beginning! The beginning of a miserable life in which I never get to be the Warden!
I'm doomed to be the Vice Warden for eternity!
Are you all right, sir? What the hell's wrong with him?
Thanks, guys.
Travis Stark!
Punt!
Straw Hat and his followers on level four!
Puggy the Cloud leading a riot on level two!
And the warlord, Blackbeard, busting through the main gates?
What should I do?
How do I even begin to deal with this mess?
This is feeling like a pretty good time to take a snack break.
Are you nuts?
We need to save the prison now!
Oh yeah?
That's easy enough for you to say.
Oh, I see.
You want to be the Vice Warden, huh?
Can you hear me?
What? Warden Magellan?
Wait, where are you?
I'm on level two, and I've just taken care of these fools.
This floor is clear.
Huh?
Somebody help me!
I've blocked off all of the exits on level two.
If the poison hasn't stopped them yet, it will soon enough.
No! We're completely blocked in!
The doorway's clogged with poison!
What do we do, Captain Buggy?
Magellan!
You obnoxious, toxic bastard!
Blast!
He'll find us if we stay here!
As for Blackbeard, I haven't a clue why he's attacking us.
Uh-huh.
But I'm already taking care of things.
Nice.
It's not something I particularly wanted to do, but I wasn't given any other options.
What do you mean it's not something you wanted to do?
Against better judgment, I decided to really sheeter you to deal with them.
Are you insane?
Possibly.
But we can't ask Navy HQ for reinforcements.
We're left with no choice but to deal with this ourselves.
And as for you, put all of your efforts into getting level four under control.
I'll be heading down to level four soon enough.
Until I get there, it's your master clean-up.
I love you, Vader.
I love you!
Order!
I love the ward!
Love the ward!
Yeah, shouldn't we be going now?
Feather.
Feather!
Yee-haw!
Hey, Krabgar!
You know where the staircase to level three is?
It's to the left, directly across that bridge!
Guard six!
Guard, out of my way!
Light!
Yes, sir!
Shiryu.
Feels good to step out of that cell, doesn't it?
Oh, yeah. It's nice. Lesson learned. All that boredom really makes you long for the excitement of death.
But you're not gonna use me as your pawn only to toss my ass back in there once you're done with me, right, Magellan?
You're a condemned prisoner. But this is your one chance.
Consider it a deferred sentence.
Yeah, right. Fine with me. I'll make sure I'm on my best behavior.
Where's your sword, Jail Manager Shiryu?
As for Blackbeard, he's all yours.
Works for me.
Gotcha!
Oh, my lovely sword.
It's been too long.
I got carried away there.
Sorry.
Undeterred by the defenses of Impel Down, the Blackbeard Pirates march onward through the prison.
Faced with an impossible dilemma, Magellan is forced to unleash a dangerous former ally to deal with the intruders.
But what will happen when Blackbeard crosses paths with the killer?
On the next, One Piece, The Dangerous Encounter, Blackbeard and Shiryu of the Ring.
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!